myefoods.com 2011-05-31

# eFoods Global - Saving Families One Meal At A Time

This Privacy Policy applies to the main Site as well as related Independent Business Owner (IBO) Sites accessed from myefoods.com. 

We are committed to protecting your privacy and using any personal information you provide responsibly. We believe it is important for you to understand what information we collect from you, how it is used and who will have access to that information.   

Information Collected   
The information we receive depends on what you do when you visit our Sites. We do not collect or retain any personal information unless you choose to provide it to us. When you visit our Site, eFoods Global, LLC collects and stores non-personally identifiable information such as:   
• the name of the domain from which you access the Internet   
• the date and time you access our Site  
• the Internet address of the website from which you linked to our Site  

eFoods Global may also use your information if you opt to receive information about eFoods Global, becoming an IBO, or purchasing or inquiring about eFoods Global products from an IBO. We use this information to track the number of visitors to the different pages of our Site as well as make our Site more convenient to users. 

If you contact us, submit ideas to us or request to be contacted by an IBO, we collect the information that you provide, which may include name, email address, postal address and telephone number. When you make a purchase from an authorized eFoods Global IBO Site, your credit card information is collected and stored only for the duration of the sale, unless you ask to have the information stored indefinitely. In addition, when you make a purchase from an authorized eFoods Global IBO Site, your billing and shipping information may be used to provide you with additional product information and offers unless you request not to receive such information.   

Information Disclosure  
We may disclose your personal information for the following purposes:   
• To our eFoods Global IBOs to provide services to you;   
• To organizations that perform services for us or on our behalf, including, without limitation, to provide customer service; process credit cards; conduct research, marketing or data processing; or to provide marketing and promotional services on our behalf, to the extent that information is necessary to provide services to us;   
• To protect the Site and our rights; to protect ourselves against liability or prevent fraudulent activity; or where it is necessary to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit any damages that we may sustain;   
• In the event of or in connection with the sale, merger, spin-off or other corporate reorganization of our corporation, where the information is provided to the new controlling entity in regular course of business;   
• If required to comply with a subpoena or warrant issued or an order made by a court, person or body with jurisdiction to compel the production of information, or to comply with the rules or court relating to the production of records; and   
• If we believe in good faith that a law, regulation, rule or guideline requires it.   

Data Security  
To prevent unauthorized use, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of information, eFoods Global has put in place appropriate physical, electronic and administrative procedures to safeguard and secure information collected online. eFoods Global is working to meet or exceed the requirements for the 12 Payment Card Industry (PCI) and Data Security Standards to ensure that any data you provide is secure.   

Changes to Privacy Policy   
We may change or supplement this Privacy Policy from time to time and we will post revised versions of this Policy on the Site. Privacy Policy changes will apply to the information collected from the date we post the revised Privacy Policy to the Site, as well as to existing information held by us.   

California Privacy Rights   
California residents have the right to request the following information from businesses with whom they have an established business relationship:   
• A list of the categories of personal information that a business has disclosed to third parties during the immediately preceding calendar year for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes if any.  
• The names and addresses of all such third parties if any  
If you are a eFoods Global IBO or customer and a California resident, please contact us at the postal address below to request this information. Please note that we are only required to respond to each IBO or customer once per calendar year.   

Contact Information   
All questions and concerns about your privacy can be sent to Privacy@eFoodsGlobal.com or 131 West 7065 South, Attn: Privacy Policy Rights, Midvale, UT 84047. 

Effective Date: September 2010
